(Girl:)You're very funny. I'm Abby.
(Sheldon:)-I'm Sheldon.
-How do you do?
(Raj:)Rajesh Ramayan Koothrappali.
Call me Raj.
-Hey, Raj. Where are you from?
-The mysterious subcontinent of India.
(Abby:)-Ooh. India.
-You know India?
(Abby:)-I saw Slumdog Millionaire.
-Well, I'm a slumdog astrophysicist.
(Sheldon:)I thought your father
was a gynecologist.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Abby:)Martha, come here.
Meet Raj and Sheldon.
(Abby:)-My friend Martha.
-Hi.
(Raj:)-Hello.
-Hello.
(Martha:)Is that the limited edition
Green Lantern lantern?
(Sheldon:)In brightest day, in darkest night,
no evil shall escape my sight.
(Martha:)Oh, that is so awesome.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Have you chosen one
to copulate with?